myjackpotcasino.com 2014-12-03

# MyJackpotCasino - Privacy Policy

You can rest assured that your information and transactions made at the Casino will be kept completely confidential. As a sign of our commitment to the privacy of our players, we have set up the following guidelines for both our website and the flash casino software and as well as any additional Casino related activities. 

_Collecting Information._

We collect, manage and use personal information solely for the benefit of providing an optimal level of service. Most of the information maintained at the Casino, is supplied by you. Some data is collected automatically by our system (such as your choice of games and payment preferences). 

_Usage of Information._

Information collected is used to protect and manage your file, account or other information. Information is also used to process your transaction and to comply with laws and regulations. All information collected by the Caisno, also helps us to design new services and improve existing ones so that we can continue to provide you with quality entertainment. Information also allows us to be able to contact you about our software, services and / or website. 

_Confidentiality of Information._

We do not give out personal information. Your personal data and account information will never be sold to a third party. 

_Non-Personal Information._

For research or promotional purposes, we may use non-personal, unspecified information to create statistics on players' activities. This can be transaction patterns, payments or gaming preferences. These activities will never include any personally identifiable information without prior consent of the player. 

_Security of Information._

We have taken various measures to protect your information. Your information is stored on secure networks and is only accessible to a select number of employees. When you have access to your personal player information, you do so through a secure connection. During the exchange of data, it uses a special coding. The technology is regularly updated to protect your information and to ensure the reliability of our systems.
